<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context=".SkillsActivity">
    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvExperienceHeader"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Experience"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:textSize="18sp"
        android:padding="10dp"
        android:background="@drawable/blue_button_background"
        android:textColor="@color/white"
        android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="10dp"
        android:layout_gravity="center" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvExperienceSubheader"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Software Engineer Trainee\nSemicolon Africa\nYaba, Lagos Nigeria\n19th September 2022 - 19th July 2023"
        android:textSize="16sp"
        android:padding="10dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/tvExperienceHeader"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/tvExperience"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="● Participated in a comprehensive training program focused on software development and engineering principles.\n\n● Collaborated with senior developers and engineers on various projects to gain hands-on experience and learn industry best practices.\n\n● Assisted in the design, development, and testing of software applications, contributing to the successful delivery of multiple projects.\n\n● Debugged and resolved software defects to improve the overall quality and functionality of the applications.\n\n● Actively participated in code reviews and provided constructive feedback to enhance code quality.\n\n● Demonstrated ability to learn new technologies quickly and apply them effectively in practical scenarios.\n\n● Worked closely with cross-functional teams to ensure alignment and successful project completion.\n\n● Developed a web-based inventory management system using Python and Django, which improved the efficiency of tracking and managing inventory for a client.\n\n● Created a data analysis tool using Java, allowing users to extract insights from large datasets and visualize the results.\n\n● Designed and implemented a responsive website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, showcasing a portfolio of personal projects."
        android:padding="5dp"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@id/tvExperienceSubheader"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent" />

</LinearLayout>
